UHCL Comiculture Collection, 2009-2013 (#2014-0005)
University of Houston-Clear Lake Archives & Special Collections
UHCL Comiculture Collection
2009-2013
2009-2012
University of Houston-Clear Lake
2014-0005
5 linear feet (1 box)
University of Houston-Clear Lake Archives & Special Collections
The Comiculture Collection contains ephemera from UHCL Comiculture event hosted by the University of Houston-Clear Lake from 2009-2013
Scope and Contents of the Records
An event card and issues of comic books related to the Comiculture event hosted by the University of Houston-Clear Lake.
Access Restrictions
Unrestricted
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Nasso, Mark; Doub, David; Brown, Leroy; Martin, Charles; Weinke, Will
Subjects
Comic books, strips, etc.; Graphic novels
Document Types
Graphic novel
Acquisition Information
Casey Roberson, Neumann Library Research and Instruction Librarian
Detailed Description of the Collection
- UHCL Comiculture Collection, 2009-2013
  - Comiculture Event Card, September 21, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - After Twilight, #1 of 6, October 2011 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - After Twilight, #2 of 6, January 2012 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - After Twilight, #3 of 6, March 2012 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - After Twilight, #4 of 6, May 2012 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - After Twilight, #5 of 6, July 2012 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - After Twilight, #6 of 6, September 2012 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dusk, Volume 1, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dusk, Volume 2, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ice Cubes, #1, Noise is News, June 2012 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Mark Nasso Illustration Collection, Volume, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Land of the Rats IV, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Las Locas 2, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Wonderboy Serials Issues 1-6, by Charles Martin and Will Weinke, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 14)